Guide to the Vassar College Baccalaureate and Commencement Records, 1867-2025
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Baccalaureate and Commencement Records
1867-2025
Vassar College
1.6 cubic feet (4 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
The collection consists of programs, invitations, song lyrics, sheet music, and other materials related to Vassar College's Spring ceremonies of commencement and the awarding of baccalaureate degrees.
Scope and Content Note
The collection consists of programs, invitations, song lyrics, sheet music, and other materials related to Vassar College's Spring ceremonies of commencement and the awarding of baccalaureate degrees.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
The Vassar College Subject Files contains additional materials related to Commencement.
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Students
Subjects:
Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
Document Types:
Printed Ephemera; Sheet music
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Events and Issues
Encoding Information
Encoded by Emma Gronbeck, November 2024. Last updated, June 2025.
Acquisition Information
An artificial collection assembled from materials separated from the Vassar College Subject Files and previously cataloged materials.
Gift of various donors.
Container List
- Baccalaureate hymns, 1894-1900 (Folder 1.1)
- Baccalaureate hymns, 1901-1909 (Folder 1.2)
- Baccalaureate hymns, 1910-1914 (Folder 1.3)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1915-1919 (Folder 1.4)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1920-1924 (Folder 1.5)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1925-1929 (Folder 1.6)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1930-1934 (Folder 1.7)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1935-1939 (Folder 1.8)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1940-1944 (Folder 1.9)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1946-1949 (Folder 1.10)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1950-1954 (Folder 1.11)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1955-1957, 1959 (Folder 1.12)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1960-1969 (Folder 1.13)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1970-1971, 1980 (Folder 1.14)
- Baccalaureate programs, 1996-1997, 1999 (Folder 1.15)
- Baccalaureate programs, 2010, 2013-2014 (Folder 1.16)
- Baccalaureate programs, 2015, 2018 (Folder 1.17)
- Baccalaureate sermons, 1871, 1882, 1889 (Folder 1.18)
- Baccalaureate sermons, circa 1913 (Folder 1.19)
- Baccalaureate sermons, 1924 (Folder 1.20)
- Baccalaureate sermons, 1939, 1941 (Folder 1.21)
- Baccalaureate sermons, 1946, 1949 (Folder 1.22)
- Baccalaureate sermons, 1951-1953 (Folder 1.23)
- Baccalaureate sermons - notes on speakers, undated (Folder 1.24)
- Baccalaureate service press releases, 1960, 1964-1966 (Folder 2.1)
- Baccalaureate service press releases, 1968-1969 (Folder 2.2)
- Baccalaureate service press releases, 1993-1996, 1999, 2004 (Folder 2.3)
- Commencement - Dinner seating charts, 1904, 1907-1908, 1913 (Folder 2.4)
- Commencement invitations and tickets, 1867-1869 (Folder 2.5)
- Commencement invitations and tickets, 1870-1871, 1896 (Folder 2.6)
- Commencement invitations and tickets, 1908, 1911, 1929 (Folder 2.7)
- Commencement invitations and tickets, 1948, 1955, 1960 (Folder 2.8)
- Commencement invitations and tickets, 1966, 1981, 2001 (Folder 2.9)
- Commencement - Procession directions, 1925, 1931-1932 (Folder 2.10)
- Commencement - Procession directions, 1935, 1938, 1950 (Folder 2.11)
- Commencement - Procession directions, 1958-1960, 1965 (Folder 2.12)
- Commencement - Procession directions, 1968-1980 (Folder 2.13)
- Commencement - Procession directions, 1984-1985, 1987-1988 (Folder 2.14)
- Commencement - Procession directions, 1991-1992, 1996 (Folder 2.15)
- Commencement programs, 1867-1869 (Folder 2.16)
- Commencement programs, 1870-1874 (Folder 2.17)
- Commencement programs, 1875-1879 (Folder 2.18)
- Commencement programs, 1880-1884 (Folder 2.19)
- Commencement programs, 1885-1889 (Folder 2.20)
- Commencement programs, 1890-1894 (Folder 2.21)
- Commencement programs, 1895-1899 (Folder 2.22)
- Commencement programs, 1900-1904 (Folder 2.23)
- Commencement programs, 1905-1909 (Folder 2.24)
- Commencement programs, 1910-1914 (Folder 2.25)
- Commencement programs, 1915-1919 (Folder 2.26)
- Commencement programs, 1920-1924 (Folder 2.27)
- Commencement programs, 1925-1929 (Folder 2.28)
- Commencement programs, 1930-1934 (Folder 2.29)
- Commencement programs, 1935-1939 (Folder 2.30)
- Commencement programs, 1940-1944 (Folder 2.31)
- Commencement programs, 1945-1949 (Folder 2.32)
- Commencement programs, 1950-1954 (Folder 3.1)
- Commencement programs, 1955-1959 (Folder 3.2)
- Commencement programs, 1960-1964 (Folder 3.3)
- Commencement programs, 1965-1969 (Folder 3.4)
- Commencement programs, 1970-1974 (Folder 3.5)
- Commencement programs, 1975-1979 (Folder 3.6)
- Commencement programs, 1980-1984 (Folder 3.7)
- Commencement programs, 1985-1989 (Folder 3.8)
- Commencement programs, 1990-1994 (Folder 3.9)
- Commencement programs, 1995-1999 (Folder 3.10)
- Commencement programs, 2000-2004 (Folder 3.11)
- Commencement programs, 2006-2007, 2009 (Folder 4.1)
- Commencement programs, 2010, 2012-2013 (Folder 4.2)
- Commencement programs, 2025 (Folder 4.2)
- Commencement - Railroad rates, 1908-1912 (Folder 4.3)
- Commencement Week programs, 1869, 1874, 1887 (Folder 4.4)
- Commencement Week programs, 1918-1921 (Folder 4.5)
- Commencement Week programs, 1922 (Folder 4.6)
- Commencement Week programs, 1924-1926 (Folder 4.7)
- Commencement Week programs, 1927-1928 (Folder 4.8)
- Commencement Week programs, 1930, 1935, 1938 (Folder 4.9)
- Commencement Week programs, 1940-1942 (Folder 4.10)
- Commencement Week programs, 1950, 1959, 1969 (Folder 4.11)
- Commencement Week programs, 1982, 1987, 1989, 1999 (Folder 4.12)